[ {
  "id" : "ea2be1f8-f183-4560-bb37-aec62d1bab95",
  "examType" : "TEST",
  "name" : "OOP",
  "questions" : [ {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 1
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 2
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c", "d" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 4
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c", "d", "e" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 5
  } ]
}, {
  "id" : "81201942-a291-4feb-aa98-a929140ae252",
  "examType" : "TEST",
  "name" : "OOP2",
  "questions" : [ {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 1
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "c", "b", "a" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 2
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "b", "a", "c" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 3
  } ]
}, {
  "id" : "d3b1b4cd-6f68-4d91-9885-27e6293b3a81",
  "examType" : "TEST",
  "name" : "OOP3",
  "questions" : [ {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 1
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c", "d" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 4
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 1
  } ]
}, {
  "id" : "d2bfaae3-9530-43c4-8c46-e3fa10332b97",
  "examType" : "TEST",
  "name" : "OOP4",
  "questions" : [ {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 1
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 1
  } ]
}, {
  "id" : "9c9ecff0-be55-490a-9aeb-4d358d2a381c",
  "examType" : "TEST",
  "name" : "OOP5",
  "questions" : [ {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 1
  }, {
    "question" : "Klausimas?\nAtsakymų variantai:",
    "answers" : [ "a", "b", "c" ],
    "correctAnswer" : 3
  } ]
} ]